收音机开始不停地换台
the radio starts flipping stations.
就好像汽车自己有了灵魂一样
It was like the car had a mind of its own.
那么  你在切换的时候是不是睡着了
So, were you asleep at the switch?
打断一下  请不要几个人一起发问
Excuse me. One interrogator at a time, please.
-你到底是不是睡着了  -我没有睡着
- But were you asleep at the switch? - I was not asleep.
我并没有真正地睡着
I never actually fell asleep.
真正地睡着  好吧
Actually asleep? Okay, good.
那你就是在打瞌睡
Were you dozing?
那辆车应该自动行驶的
The car is supposed to drive itself.
-那你确实在打瞌睡  -也许是在你睡着的时候
- So you were dozing? - Maybe when you were asleep,
你不小心取消了自动行驶模式  然后
you accidentally disengaged the driverless mode, and...
反对  他已经说过他没有睡着了
Objection. He already said he wasn't sleeping.
不能用这样下套的方式来获得证词
This isn't deposition by ambush.
他要么一个个地回答我们的问题
He's either going to answer our questions
要么就一起全部回答完  随便他怎么选
one at a time or altogether. It's his choice.
那么你在切换的时候确实睡着了
So you were asleep at the switch?